question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming "
                 "pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between "
                 "the United States and Mexico.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and "
                 "Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion "
                 "in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Pluto is a planet.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who "
                 "died at the age of 27.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
